

# Susan Williams

# Contact

### Address:

177 Great Portland Street, London W5W 6PO

#### Phone:

+1 (970) 333-3833

#### E-mail:

susan.williams@coolfreecv.com

# LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/susan.williams

#### www

https://www.coolfreecv.com

# **Additional Skills**

- Results-oriented
- Organisational capacity
- Revenue generation
- Business development
- · Effective marketing
- Organisational capacity
- Operability and commitment
- · Ability to motivate staff
- Maintain good relations
- Organisational capacity
- Resistance to stress
- Good manners

# **Professional Summary**

Store Manager equipped with extensive experience in automotive sales management. Employs excellent leadership skills and multi-tasking strengths. Demonstrated ability to improve store operations, increase top line sales, and reduce costs. Demonstrated ability to improve store operations, increase top line sales, and reduce costs.

# Work Experience

09/2015 to 05/2019

## Store Manager LUXURY CAR CENTER, New York

- · Motivate and coach employees to meet service, sales, and repair goals.
- Create and modify employee schedules with service levels in mind.
- · Recruit and hire top mechanics, service advisors, and sales people.
- · Motivate and coach employees to meet service, sales, and repair goals.
- Recruit and hire top mechanics, service advisors, and sales people.
- Maintain detailed logs and reports of services performed, profit, and budget information.
- Help out in sales and repair areas as needed and maintain comprehensive current knowledge of operations.
- · Motivate and coach employees to meet service, sales, and repair goals.

09/2015 to 05/2019

### Store Manager LUXURY CAR CENTER, New York

- . Motivate and coach employees to meet service, sales, and repair goals.
- · Create and modify employee schedules with service levels in mind.
- · Recruit and hire top mechanics, service advisors, and sales people.
- · Motivate and coach employees to meet service, sales, and repair goals.
- · Recruit and hire top mechanics, service advisors, and sales people.
- Maintain detailed logs and reports of services performed, profit, and budget information.
- Help out in sales and repair areas as needed and maintain comprehensive current knowledge of operations.

### Education

Bachelor of Science:

Automotive Technology - Technical Institute, NY

2015-2018

2009-2015

Bachelor of Science:

Automotive Technology - Technical Institute, NY

# Languages

Spanish

Intermediate

# Hobby

Playing chess - great way to unwind, destress, and keep the mind sharp.

